Within the City of Osaka, Osaka, Japan,
Due to the earthquake within the city of Osaka, Japan
Now I would like to start the rehearsal. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Please do.
Let me greet you first.
Seino, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6,
To the hearts of the staff, lock on!
We are Super Scimeci NM. Please give us your best regards.
Please give us your best regards.
I saw you on stage for the first time today at the rehearsal,
It was the cutest show ever.
It was so cute that I thought it was someone else's show,
I was so cute that I thought it was someone else's live performance,
I was attracted to her at that point,
The heart balloon,
The color of the heart balloons seemed to change with love and youth,
I'm really looking forward to that.
If only I could prepare for the site,
I'm sure you will comment on it!
Highly difficult,
I'm sorry, but I can't help but laugh at the video. pain screaming
I'm laughing too.
I'm not moving back to Tokyo.
I'm going to start from here.
Get out of here, go this way, go this way.
Properly cross over.
Up the stairs, up the other stairs, back to the stage.
That's where you can't see everyone at dinner.
Mom and Kanami are settled in. We're much closer, so let's just relax and go.
That's awfully close.
Sorry, it's heavy coming out today.
On the other hand, Hitokata is quite a bit higher up, came by the same route, and went straight to the geography...
If we sit here, it's so close.
Hitokata, let's just turn there.
Yes.
Turn there...
But it's easy to see.
The stage.
Yes, it is.
I'm going to put an orange A-melody before the A-melody.
Yoo-hoo!
Good morning.
I really appreciate it.
The day I heard your voice over and over again.
Each percent range
It's gonna end the same way.
The day I raised my hand to this heart
When I put my words in your voice
I met you.
LaLaLa...
Lalala...
LaLaLaLaLaLaLa...
LaLaLaLaLaLaLaLaLa...
Maybe we should go a little slower... on foot.
Julia and the others got here too fast.
I've been waiting a long time.
And before that, the part about going to the roulette table...
I'm finally going to float.
Oh, my God.
I have to keep my head in the game.
Okay, I'll bring it up.
I'll go with you.
I'll lift you up, Mema.
Yes, please.
First day, ice cream, ice cream.
Oh, my God.
Cool.
It'll go high.
Pretty high.
Congratulations
Congratulations.
So this is the highest point.
There will be one more after this, so I will try to move in this basic position.
We'll move. Please.
Forward!
Oh!
It's going like this!
I'm not even walking.
Wow, wow, wow!
That's pretty fast.
This fast?
This fast.
That's the basic speed.
Oh, check!
I want to check the hole.
Wow!
Amazing stage!
It's amazing!
It's like an attraction!
This is the basic speed.
Yes, I went!
I was really looking forward to the moving stage,
But when I got up on the stage, I was more scared than I thought I would be.
I didn't know what to expect from different members,
I think I was a little scared,
I was a little scared.
I like attractions, but I was a little scared,
But when it comes to dancing, singing, etc,
I had to concentrate on various things,
You have to concentrate on various things,
I had to concentrate on various things, like where to stand, where to be, and so on,
I have a lot of things on my mind.
Maybe on stage,
I'm planning to stand on the stage with a relaxed smile on my face, but I think I'm panicking,
But I think my head is in a panic.
So I really need to concentrate,
I hope I can make some changes,
I hope I can make some changes.
I want to bring out those things and have more confidence in myself.
It was really a lot of fun.
I thought it would be really fun to go up like this and sing and dance while looking at so many different audiences,
I thought it would be a lot of fun to get up there and sing and dance while watching so many different kinds of people, so I was very happy to participate.
The moving stage was not as scary as I thought it would be,
I thought it would be scarier, even though Calamine and Pio are good at screaming,
I was pretty good at it even though I can't do screams,
I was surprised that I could do it. But I have to be careful with the start of the show.
I have to be careful about that.
It's pretty fun. It's like being in a vehicle.
Yes, it's fun.
Don't fall off!
Don't fall off, Aki-chan.
Yes, the decision will be made.
I'm going to move up to the center stage.
Yes, sir.
Okay, up you go.
Amazing.
When you get the furthest you can fly.
Where do I fall?
Where do I drop it? Drop?
Drop?
Oh, I'm losing it.
Here we go.
Oh, shit.
It's not moving at all.
It's too light. It won't fly.
Throw it from one to the other.
Oh, my God!
I'm terrible at this!
I suck at this!
I'm really bad at this!
Even if I throw really hard, it doesn't fly very far.
Try not to swing it too hard and it won't fall.
Yes, sir.
Oh, it arrived!
It arrived!
I got it.
It didn't go this far.
Where, where, where, where, where?
When they get this far, they want to do it.
Oh, great.
Here we go.
I'm afraid the technical staff is going to get crushed.
So you have no choice but to land?
Yes, sir.
Right under us.
You're right below us?
I'll set up a crew right below you.
Yes, please.
Right below you.
Please, sir.
Please.
Huh.
That was great.
Taller. Stand up better.
I can do it.
I can do it! I can do it!
You're doing great.
That's great.
Mom, can you get to the gray line when you're moving?
I can!
Can you?
I can dance!
Muti-muti.
I'm going to be tough.
There's a scary girl in there.
Just tell me...
Tell me now how many times you love me I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you I love you
Amaza Amazara
Blue, blue, blue, corner of my heart
Yes, I'm sure you'll be there
Ladies and gentlemen
Good luck, okay
Thank you for your time.
Thank you for watching.
Because I care. You don't want to believe me.
I'm just really tired.
Batta ima ke batta, repeat.
Don't tell me now with the dance
I'm in love with you, but I'm not in love with the lights
I'm the cutest thing in the world right now
I'm the cutest thing in the world now that you dumped me
This is how a girl strikes back.
This way!
Right here. She's passing through here.
I don't know if you can go through there, but when you go behind it, it's a little higher up.
You mean they're going to go through there first? Yeah, we'll wait a bit.
Can we just go with the flow? One more time.
I wanted to keep you waiting.
I want to make you wait forever... so spread the joy.
You and me, our FINAL SONG
Everyone who obeys our rules, let's go forward!
Let's go out today, blooming day by day, now clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds, clouds
It's just me
Gentlemen Who Obey the Rules, Let's Go Ahead, Bloom Every Day, Let's Go Today, Ima Kumo Kumo no Saikousei
Just keep the rules, everyone, let's go forward!
Hello, hello to endless possibilities
Let's try all the things we want to do
I'll introduce you all
FINAL SONG
We'll be using
Don't go tomorrow
Pavlin
Pavlin...
I want you to get off before we leave on the chorus of WANTED.
Pavlin.
I missed getting off.
Oh, my God!
I missed the exit.
I can't do it anymore.
But I don't know why I'm here.
I missed the fold.
If you're in the boat, I'm going with you.
I'm going with you.
We'll come back together when the show's over.
We'll be back together when the show comes.
Something about you breaking up...
It was nice.
I'm gonna go for a walk.
I'm having fun.
Lifter.
Yes, well, we'll end rehearsal once and for all.
Thank you very much for the rehearsal.
And thank you for the investment rehearsal.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you very much.
Rehearsal is over!
Still rehearsing, because the investment rehearsal is coming up.
It's cute, but I, I don't know how to breathe in the new song
It's a 6. If you're soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Pass 6
No, no, no. One, two, three, four, five.
I hope you'll change it.
But after that, in the middle?
Don't you want to sit there?
No, I'm not sitting there.
It's cheap.
What do you think? You don't know?
No.
What future intonation do you have?
Intonation I don't know yet
The set is so cute!
I feel like I'm in outer space.
I think the costumes are going to look great.
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to seeing the costumes.
I still don't know...
I have an impression that I don't know yet.
I have an impression that fans haven't shown yet.
I'm looking forward to seeing their reactions.
Your bento has changed.
I ate the bento.
Your bento's changed too.
Where did that go?
It went a while ago.
See you.
me
me.
Me.
Yeah, about four cameramen all came to me at once when I said that.
Free Spitz, very nice, very plain...
Oh, hey!
It's a rehearsal.
Omoshiiri...
We're going to start the rehearsal.
It's pretty much the
feeling on the lesson and always put a lot of ballerinas on the lesson,
I couldn't take pictures of the actual performance, so I had to use my imagination,
I was imagining how the line of flow would be here,
I was told that the line of flow was like this, and that when you move from the main stage to the muted stage, you can move to the center of the stage or the far end of the stage,
I would hear the voices and the back of the stage differently as I moved from the main stage to the center or the far end of the stage,
I checked this in my dream,
Of course, I have not been able to perform all of the songs at this stage,
I am sometimes a little nervous about how Inagi will be able to take the first step,
I imagine that we are all going to be in a space where we are all waiters,
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow.
Yes, there are many things I can do for the first time with this investment,
I've never been able to do anything like this before, not even on the lessons,
I can't do it at all.
There were so many things I couldn't do,
I hope I can do my best today to make sure I'm not too excited and to make sure I'm not too anxious tomorrow,
I'll do my best to check it properly without getting too excited today, so that I can get rid of my anxiety for tomorrow.
There are many parts of the new songs that are a bit difficult to sing,
I'll make sure to check that too, and also check the clicks and so on carefully.
But I've been told that I'm not off by much at all,
But I think I'll be fine as long as I keep it up, so I'm just going to enjoy myself.
The zipper on the back of the costume,
There was nothing on it,
You can see it, can't you?
Can you see it?
You can see the rest of this part.
It's cute.
Your mind is familiar.
That's important.
That's right.
You've backed me up.
You agreed with me.
You've been in on the conversation before.
I heard he's been talking to the pub.
Let's get started.
I don't want to be the only one who's getting caught. I want everyone to know what's going on.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I don't want to keep saying things like, "Let's have fun.
I don't like that.
We're all going up.
Music
Adjust the tone of the Garmin by color
trabal manageable
price problem
manual car
I'm going all out with this thing.
Go!
cross the street, walk, walk, walk!
It's really something,
It's a big stage called "YOKOARI".
We were even more determined to do our best to not lose to it.
I was even more determined to do my best to live up to it.
It was a very strange feeling,
It was so strange that it didn't really feel like it was just us and Pavlin on the stage.
I couldn't really feel that it was just us and Pavlin on the stage.
It was so gorgeous that it didn't really feel like it was just us and Pavlin on the stage,
It was like we were at a real festival.
So it was really strange,
So, we are all on the ground,
I think it would be great if we could get our feet on the ground and let everyone know that this is a live show just for us.
I hope that tomorrow and the day after tomorrow, everyone will understand with a bang that we are performing on our own.
I want to give a magnificent performance so that everyone can understand that we are the only live band.
Only a lot!
Together.
Always and always.
Dan!
You don't even want me.
Please don't spoil me.
Don't look at me sideways.
Just look at me.
Right now.
me
Rar.
4 days
7 days
Happy happy happy happy lover love
It was you
me
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
I'm embarrassed to see this.
Hang in there, Hiyori.
You're sparkling.
Newcomer oh oh oh.
hiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiii
Night MINant
rein
Beautiful song est Reserve
Hm...
Now all that's left is for you and me to do something fun with our youth.
Doing something fun
If I said I was going to leave out some parts of the song, I would have sung them without leaving out any parts that I thought were good.
Doing Youth with You
The part before that is higher.
Are you okay? Bangs.
Oh, you look fine.
Not at all. I'm just setting myself today.
It looks good.
I'm going to copy you.
real
화
ahhhhh!
ah ah ah ah
car
yes
happy happy happy love blue
What do you say?
I want to be with you
the night moves on
Wish come true magic
I'll hold you in my arms
In love
We'll get through this
I hold you in my arms
In love
It's not impossible
To think of you
I can't hide the tears
Forever
I'm aware of your speed, so much so that it doesn't bother me.
Love Potion
I don't know what to do, even for a minute
Forget it after all, you can't do it forever
Is it love?
I don't want to be scared here waiting for you.
I don't want to be scared...
Animalis bibittila
Hey, hey, hey!
hey
me
I want to eat rice and eat elbow grease.
Thank you all very much. I look forward to working with you tonight.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
I'm not sleepy.
I'm sleepy and hungry.
Excited! Excited!
Good morning!
We are waiting for you!
Thank you very much!
Don't worry, we will call you in front of TikTok in front of the photo!
I flew in today.
Thank you for your hard work!
I know the round looked like a real production, but...
It's a great relief to be able to look back over the day like this!
I guess all we have to do now is just to enjoy it.
I did my best!
But the sound was really difficult.
The monitors, you know...
If you have a big stage, you have to deal with outside noise and sound problems.
I'm sure we've all found our issues.
I'll make sure to get a good night's sleep.
But I'm going to do my best to review and make sure we can do it tomorrow.
I'm sure we'll do our best.
We'll do our best.
But you know, if we do it tomorrow, the two days will be over in no time.
I thought today's rehearsal would be over in no time.
It happened so fast.
Two days go by so fast!
I haven't been rehearsed in 3 years...
I haven't done it in four years, and then it's over.
I'm already looking forward to it.
The monitor for the video is really beautiful.
I think everyone who sees it will be thrilled, and some people will cry a lot.
Please look forward to it!
Please look forward to it.
Yes, sir!
It's Mr. Taku Mori, isn't it?
There are 50 of us.
Once it started, it all happened so fast.
It all happened so fast.
The costumes, too.
There were a lot of costume changes.
I was thinking we'd like to do a few more encores.
Roulette.
Roulette is fun.
I'm starting to feel like I'm having fun.
There are a lot of new songs.
There's a freshness to it.
You can feel the excitement.
Julia's favorite performance is
India.
I love that.
Solo.
There's some kind of white light
Floating through space behind my back.
The universe behind my back
When I look back with the six of us
Six people having fun
But Julia, you're not the only one
Colors to the new shark
With a group of people
So
It's going to be fast.
You're lying.
We'll check it out, too, at the show.
The love performance tomorrow. We just did it through.
However, I'll do my best again tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep, eat, and work hard.
I've changed some things in preparation for tomorrow, but there's a marker called "hot meal,
Don't get your hopes up.
There has never been a hot meal.
Basically, you know, sometimes I think hot meal because there hasn't been one lately, and there's an arrow.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
Yay!
I like the way the world changes.
I like the way the world is changing.
Isn't the energy transmission going to be intense for a long time?
I can feel what's inside.
I can feel the inside of you.
I'm going to continue to run with your youth.
I don't know why, but when I laugh
It's like the world is shining.
I can turn the umbrella around and take it easy
I can't walk if I don't
Surely somewhere someone is crying
And somewhere I'll get my body wet again
I hope it's not too cold
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying
Just a little bit of my feelings
I want to share it with you
I still don't know what's in front of me
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the cityscape turns color
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future
And it's guiding me on the way
I can say it now
Whenever you're lost, just remember the reason for your tears
And when it's raining, I'll smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, making puddles of sound
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, I'm so proud of my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
I'm gonna wear a rainbow dress
I'll wear my rainbow dress
Lalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalalala
Please subscribe to our channel!